Dr. Shahid Hussain

Karachi, Sind(en), 75300 | +92-333-0311333 | shah8635@gmail.com

Summary

Analytical, detail-oriented healthcare professional offering over 20 years of success in roles such as In-charge, teacher and Senior Medical Officer in the Department of Medical Emergency. Dedicated to upholding clinical guidelines, standards and best practices. Extensive experience in evaluating clinical data, compiling reports, conducting patient and staff evaluations, developing successful care plans, and managing medium to large medical staff. Dependable, patient-focused leader with proven record in organization, communication, networking and management skills.

Experience

Aug. 2019 – Present

SMO (ER) | Memon Medical Complex | Karachi

May 2012 - Present

RMO (Emergency) | KIHD, CEC Shah Faisal | Karachi

Mar. 2012 – May. 2012

In-charge (Emergency) | KKF Genral Hospital | Karachi

Mar. 2011- Mar. 2012

SMO (Emergency) | KKF General Hospital | Karachi

Dec. 2007 - Feb. 2011

In-charge / CMO | Soha Medical Center | Karachi

Dec. 2002 - Nov. 2007

SMO | Memon Medical Complex | Karachi

- Skills
- 1. Communication Skulls
- 2. Team Management & Administration
- 3. MS Office
- 4. Task Planning and Management
- Languages
- 1. Urdu | Native Speaker
- 2. Sindhi | Fluent
- 3. Punjabi | Conversational
- 4. Baluchi | Conversational

Education

 DOW University of Health Sciences, Karachi, Sind

M.B.B.S, Medicine, Gastroenterology | Dec. 1997

- Cadet College Petaro, Jamshoro, Sind Intermediate, Science 1991
- Cadet College Petaro, Jamshoro, Sind Matric, Science, 1989

Oct. 2000 - Nov. 2002

RMO | KKF General Hospital | Karachi

Feb. 1999 – Aug. 2000

House Officer | Abbasi Shaheed Hospital | Karachi

Jul. 1998 – Dec. 1998

House Job, General Medicine | Civil Hospital | Karachi

Jan. 1998 – Jun. 1998

House Job, Surgery | Civil Hospital | Karachi